Look at this
Mira qué
gossip, strong
chismes strong
remix, Google
remix googly
Jellyfish, okay, with just
jellyfish vale con solo se supone que
that
con solo ese
promo, it's supposed to generate that, it's
prom genera
really cool,
eso está muy guapo
huh? It's better than Gen 3, it's super
eh está mejor que el Gen 3 está
cool. Well, finally, the Sora announcement arrives.
guapísimo bueno por fin llega anunci de
And what Sora? And from the creators of
sora Y qué sora y de los creadores de
Chat GPT comes Sora, the new
chat gpt llega sora la nueva ía de Open
OpenEye. And yes, the truth is that there was a lot of
eye Y sí la verdad es que había mucho
hype with this, and let's see it together, huh?
hype con esto y vamos a verlo juntos eh
Look, I go here to Google, Sora, and I
Mira me meto aquí en Google sora y me
go into whatever OpenEye time it is, there are a lot of
meto en el que sea hora de Open Ey que
weird ones, and look, a
hay muchos raros y fíjate bu sale un
lot of things come up, it looks super cool. This
montón de cosas sale guapísimo esto
would be, let's say, the Gen 4 vibe, brutal,
sería vamos el rollo del Gen 4 brutal
brutal,
brutal
what graphic quality, keep scrolling.
qué calidad gráfica sig haciendo scroll
And look, Replay, remove, Imagine elements,
Y fíjate Replay remove Imagine elements
With Your video, with remix. Look, the
With Your video with remix Mira la
first part, on the same video, you
primera parte sobre un mismo vídeo se le
can give instructions, so
pueden dar instrucciones por lo tanto
take the video that's there as a reference and you
coge de referencia el vídeo que hay y le
say, "Hey, now change the doors," and you're going to
dices Oye ahora cámbiale las puertas y
put, well, instead of the
le vas a poner Pues en lugar de las las
doors it has, the French doors,
puertas que tiene las puertas francesas
instead of a library, let's put
en lugar de una biblioteca vamos a poner
a spaceship, you paste it and a
una nave del espacio pegas y entra una
spaceship enters.  Hey, put a jungle in
naada del espacio Oye méteme una jungla
there. Okay, so a jungle, I mean, I know you're
ahí Vale pues una jungla o sea sé que le
changing it based on a first
vas cambiando sobre una primera
reference, okay, recat, the recat here, okay,
referencia vale recat el recat aquí vale
you take any frame, okay, the
tú coges cualquier frame vale el
original is this, yce St before, or this
original es este yce St before o Este
nafta, okay, this nafta is what
nafta vale que este nafta es que
extends, I mean, imagine what's going to
extienda o sea que se Imagine lo que va
happen next, and this before, what's going to
a pasar después y este before lo que va
happen before, okay, pa pa pa, organize the
a pasar antes vale pa pa pa organiza las
sequences, wah, okay, you tell it how many
secuencias wah vale le dices Cuántos
frames, okay, from frame 0 to frame 114, this is going to
frames vale de El frame cer al frame 114
happen with the ship, but then
va a pasar esto con la nave pero luego
from 114 to 324, this is going to happen, and from this
del 114 al 324 va a pasar esto y de este
frame to this frame, this other thing is going to happen, okay, I mean, you
frame a este frame va a pasar esto otro
can tell it like this. How
vale o sea se lo puedes decir así Qué
cool, okay, it's a new way of prompting, what they
guapo vale es una nueva manera de promp
bring from prompting, prompting is the
pear lo que traen de promar promar es el
verb of making prompts, prompting refers
verbo de hacer proms promp pear dígase
to the action of making
de la acción de hacer
prompts, and then, let's
proms y luego a
see, down and create repeating videos
ver down and create s repeating videos
with, which means we can make
with que quiere decir que podemos hacer
looped videos, Loop means
vídeos en bucle Loop quiere decir
loop, okay, what else? Blend,
bucle Vale qué más cosas Blend esto lo
we saw this also in Journey, but with
veíamos también en m Journey pero con
images. Now I can  Blend, that is,
las imágenes Ahora puedo blende o sea
mix two videos. Here are the snowflakes
mezclar dos vídeos aquí los snowflakes
with the flowers, and the flowers that look like
con las flowers y la flowers que parecen
butterflies, but oh well.
butterflies pero bueno
Oh, the mammoth and the rhino, and the mammoth and the
Oh El mamut y el rino y el mamut y el
rhino, and the mammoth and the rhino, and okay. We're
rino y el mamut y el rino y vale Le
changing it, okay? And we can see here a
cambiando vale Y podemos ver aquí un
mammoth with a rhino made of cardboard
mamut con rino hecho de de carb
papercraft, which is cardboard and origami paper.
papercraft que es de cartón y y de papel
Pricing includes it with the 200
pricing lo incluyen con el plan de 200
euro plan, damn, that's no small price, but also
pavos que menos no pero también
with the 20 euro GPT Plus chat that
con el chat gpt Plus de 20 pavos que
many of us pay for, and they give us 50
pagamos muchos de nosotros y nos dan 50
priority videos and stuff. And now you'll say, "Hey, it can't be done." I say, "
priority vídeos y tal Y ahora dirás oye
Relax." And yes, it has
que no se puede poner digo Tranquilo Y
n't been made available for all
sí yora no ha sido puesto para todos los
countries, but we're going to do a
países pero vamos a hacer un
trick. We'll use a VPN, for
y un tru Es que le metemos una VPN por
example, from Argentina, and you'll stop being a
ejemplo de Argentina y dejas de ser un
noob,
revolo
you understand? We're going to Argentina because
entendiste nos vamos a Argentina porque
Solora works in Argentina and
en Argentina sí funciona solora y en
not in Spain, so don't make this big
España no así que no cometas este grave
mistake. And you
error
go
y y y y te metes
here, but what happens? Account creation
aquí pero qué pasa account creation
[Music]
[Música]
And here you have to be able to log in,
y aquí tienes que poder meterte en el
and we click on login to enter.
login y le damos a login para entrar en
Sora continued with
sora continuo con
Google. And now it tells you that you can't do it.
Google Y ahora te dice que no puedes
Well, of course it's jammed. Okay. Well, right now
t Bueno claro que está petad Vale Bueno
at least it tells me that it's
ahora mismo por lo menos me dice que
jammed. Okay, that there are a lot of people,
está petado vale que hay muchísima gente
obviously they're launching it now and everyone
obvio lo están estrenando ahora y todo
is there. Tap tap tap tap tap. But
Dios está ahí Taca taca Taca taca Pero
remember that if you want to get in
recuerda que si te quieres meter
you need to use a VPN because
necesitas usar una VPN porque de otra
otherwise it's going to kick you out. And you won't be able to
manera te va a echar Y no vas a poder
use Sora. It looks really good. Well, we
usar sora tiene muy buena pinta bueno
'll have to wait a bit until
habrá que esperar un poco a que deje de
others who got there first stop using it and
usarlo otros que han llegado primero y
we can use this, which I think is
podamos usar esto que me parece que es
amazing. The quality, the hyperrealism,
una pasada la calidad el hiperrealismo
the movements. I
los movimientos
see it as much better, a priori, than Minimax, than
lo veo bastante mejor a priori que
Clean, than Runway, than
minimax que Clean ahí que runway que
Mochi,
Mochi
and there was another one out there that I don't remember
y había otra por ahí que no me acuerdo
which one it was, but I see it as much, much
cuál era pero lo veo bastante bastante
better. I mean, the guy with the hair, well, it's
mejor o sea el tipo con los pelos bueno
done
está hecho
brilliantly, brilliantly, what consistency! Wow, the
genial genial qué consistencia ostras el
focus and the
enfoque y el
blur, wow! How good!
desenfoque ostras Qué bueno
[Music]
[Música]
I think
Me parece
this is, well, great. Well, just like I just
que esto está vamos genial bueno así
showed you Sora and I
como te acabo de enseñar el sora y te he
showed you Truck, and you have to get in with a VPN
enseñado el Truck y de meterte por VPN
because otherwise you won't be able to get in
porque si no no vas a poder meterte
because it's not available in your country.  Available!
porque en tu país no está disponible
Leave me a like, forward it to lots of
déjame un pedazo de like reenvíalo mucha
people so we can start using this, and we
gente para que empecemos a usar esto y
really need to get on board because it has so
de verdad hay que darle caña porque
much potential. Save it
promete promete muchísimo guárdatelo
so you don't forget, and keep
para que no se te olvide y no dejes de
following me to continue learning about Big
seguirme para seguir aprendiendo de Big
Data and Artificial Intelligence in your daily life.
Data Inteligencia artificial en tu día a